So, so Zohra Mamdani might win tonight.
And even though he has been showing signs of liberal BS, it still would piss them off, right?
So my question to y'all is, what, what are you going to do differently if he wins?
Because you've now seen Democrats actively say, we not supporting that.
So what are you going to do differently?
And I don't mean just people in New York.
What are you going to do differently?
Because they've actively said, we're not going to support him.
And yet, some of y'all are still going to support Democrats.
And so are you going to ask yourself, why didn't they want to support him?
What are you going to do differently?
How are you going to hold them accountable?
Because that's the thing people love to talk about.
We're going to hold someone so accountable.
How?
In what way are you going to hold him accountable?
Because that's the thing.
I think that a lot of people are going to look at him winning and be like, so someone here said he can't do anything he says.
Just want to understand why y'all are so confident in your fear.
I want to understand that.
Why are y'all so confident in your fear?
Because I don't under, I can't, and so it's like, I can't relate to it.
And I really struggle with trying to have grace for it.
I really do.
I genuinely struggle because I have irrational courage.
So I'm trying to understand, like, what is, what is, what do you think the fear does for you?
How, how, how, how are you making your fear work for you?
This is what I'm trying to, like, the practical application.
Because we, I don't, I, I, I can't, I can't make it make sense.
Is it helpful?
Do you feel like you're safer if you remain afraid and silent?
Do you, do you feel like you're more secure if you put all of your trust in somebody who you literally don't even know aside from their campaigning?
I'm just trying to, like, understand because his policies are practical.
So let's start with that.
When you say his policies are not practical, that means that your limits, your, your imagination is impractical.
So, you know, it, it's, it doesn't make sense to me.
Um, so I, I don't, so like, I don't want to hear that because that's not useful to me.
When you all talk about, like, we need to stand up and demand our government and tax return and tax reform.
You sound silly to me, right?
Because the language that you're using is language of oxymoronic language.
We need to demand tax reform.
You're making a demand to have taxes?
Like, that's silly to me.
What does your reform look like?
Because they didn't want to pay taxes and now we're paying taxes and they're not used to any, for anything that we're used, that we are needing.
Snap benefits are cut illegally.
And they're only going to fund half of them after the federal judge was like, what are you doing?
There is contingency.
There is money for, for Snap.
And the, come on, the, uh, what agency is that?
The USDA just told the, the supermarkets that they are not allowed to have discounted items for Snap individual, for individuals who Snap was canceled.
Trying to understand, because, like, I've got Zionists trying to shut down, like, me doing a free tour.
Right?
Like, they're literally trying to shut that down.
And then I'm like, okay, so now I need to go even harder.
And I also want to just take a moment to say that we need to show up for our comrades in a multitude of ways.
And it is very imperative that we learn how to show up for our comrades in a physical level, um, in a monetary level, and in an emotional level.
Yes, the podcast is over.
And that's going to require you showing up for yourselves in that way, for yourselves in that way.
For the record, if someone tells you, like, hey, right now, I don't feel heard, and I don't feel supported, I just feel like, then you say, okay, what do you need from me to feel supported?
You said that already.
So, um, it's not about shaming people on Snap.
It's not about shaming people on Snap.
Who gives a fuck about shaming people on Snap?
No.
They want people on Snap to Snap.
Okay?
They don't give a damn about hurting your feelings.
They want you to Snap.
So they can literally pop off, incarcerate people, enforce martial law, etc.
They want individuals on Snap to Snap.
That this government is still human.
Like, you still think about them like, like individuals who are like you.
And that's the part that y'all really don't get.
They do not see you as a person.
They don't see you as a person.
Do you understand me?
Listen to me.
They don't see you.
They do not see you.
Which is why any time there has ever been any even semblance of forward motion in this nation,
it is when we have weapons.
And no, it hasn't always been when we were raising the Civil War was the first time
that Black people were able to be free with weapons because they were in the war.
And so, they were like, oh, y'all are people.
Y'all are people.
Next thing you know, the abolitionist movement that had been going on for years
all of a sudden started to pick up steam.
Watch the movie Lincoln.
Just watch the beginning of the movie Lincoln.
Also, stop asking me op questions on this fucking app.
Stop.
You all sound like the cop in the club.
Like, hey, anybody know where I can find some blow?
Stop asking me operative questions.
Roy's in the hood.
And I don't give a fuck if y'all want me to scream or not.
Get the fuck on.
I don't care.
Stop.
Now, if you want to support the shit I'm doing, go to amandaseals.com.
If you want to subscribe to my Patreon, it's $5.
And if you want to, I don't even know what to say.
I'm excited to see y'all in the flesh.
I really am.
So, I'm looking forward to seeing y'all in the flesh and, you know, working with y'all as we continue to fortify each other.
Really.
And I, my book, What Would the Ancestors Say?
I'm very proud of it.
I'm very emotional today.
I'm not sure why.
I'm going to ask Laura Chung what's going on with the sun and the stars and all that shit, all that shites.
But maybe I'm anxious about going tomorrow.
I'm not afraid.
You know what I'm afraid of?
I'm afraid that y'all are so afraid that you really will fuck it up for everybody.
I think that's what I'm more afraid of than anything.
No, no, Sonia.
Is it Sonia or Sandra?
I always forget.
Sometimes I feel like a soul sent here to do a job that I'm not completing for no fault of my own.
And it feels crazy.
So I'm going to continue eating my sausage, egg, and cheese.
But I actually want to share a really positive story.
So I had talked to this woman at this church around my way because I want to help volunteer at their food bank.
And so we were talking and then she was like, you know, we're trying to figure out how to get turkeys for people.
And in my effort to extend my energy and my health, because I really do believe that it's so often that the issue isn't whether or not you can.
It's that you just ain't trying to figure out how to.
So I always say the community is inconvenient because like for a lot of the shit that you're doing for your community, like it's not convenient.
You none of us really have time, but you you have more time than you think.
So I really set myself in motion like, all right, I'm gonna try and solve this.
And I'd legit could not figure out like, how am I going to get these people these turkeys?
And then I felt so bad.
I felt so bad that I was like, I'm gonna have to bow out.
I'm gonna have to bow out because I don't know how to get these people these turkeys.
And it was the it was one of the few times that I really don't have time.
I can't even like just make it I can't even like create it out of thin air.
Like I genuinely just don't have time.
And, and, and then I had to, I had to tell her like, I, I, I'm so sorry.
Like I overextended myself and I really misled the ability to do this.
I really apologize.
And, you know, I'm genuinely like remorseful.
And she was like, I'm just happy you even cared enough to want to try.
And then I went over there because I hadn't even met her in person.
I went over to the church and she met me with such a hug.
And then I spoke to the bishop on the phone and I met the other folks that helped with the pantry.
And like, that's what Christian, like, and I had told her, I was like, you know, I'm not a Christian.
I just want to help.
Stop calling me Mandy.
I said, I'm not a Christian.
I just want to help.
And I don't adhere to the Christian faith, but I live in the act of what I understand Jesus's teachings to be about.
And she was like, well, baby, that's all that matters.
Like, that's all that matters.
And she was like, and I guess for me, it was really beautiful to see, like, this is what it's supposed to be.
This is what Christianity is supposed to be.
This is what any organized religion that is grounded, that is supposedly grounded in humanism is supposed to be, right?
Because it's not even supposed to matter.
And so I met them and they just showed me so much love.
And I did cut them a check, you know, to at least give something.
I'm going to put up a flyer.
If you want to try to order a turkey and send to them, I'm sure they would appreciate it.
But the beauty in that moment was, you know, I was honest about my failure because I did fail.
And I think that's the other part is like, when you say you're going to help, when you say you're going to do something, like, sometimes you can't.
There has to also be an expression, an extension of apology and of awareness of the way that you are not able to show up.
And I had somebody fail me this week that really was on some like, yeah, whatever.
And it felt, it made me feel a way because it was like, damn, like, I understand if shit pop up, but like, you don't even give a fuck about how that affects me at all.
You're not even, I don't even exist in your consciousness.
So now that person is, and I felt so, um, just upset at myself at not being reliable.
And I was really just thankful.
I was so thankful that, that she didn't take it personal, you know, and that she didn't think that I was, um, she didn't take it as like a failure in character.
Cause so often that's what happens, right?
Like no good deed is unpunished.
So, um, I, I really appreciated that exchange, right?
Cause it's not transactional.
Like none of this shit should be transactional.
None of it should be transactional.
I'm gonna put the flyer in my bio.
And if you want to order them a turkey and send them a turkey, if you got an extra $38, you know, they would really appreciate it.
Um, as you know, the SNAP benefits is not popping off and I don't quote me on this, but I wouldn't be surprised if the states, because they said they're only going to fund 50% of SNAP benefits.
And I wouldn't be surprised if that 50% is the states that are considered blue states, the 50% they don't fund.
This is in Nyack, New York.
So that was a really appreciate.
I really appreciated that moment and the extension of kindness.
Um, I just have a lot of emotions today.
It's not upstate.
It's like outside the city, but it's not upstate.
And, um, see, this is the thing that confuses me.
Like, where do you want, where, where are y'all?
Someone just said, how can they not give to all, no matter who you vote for?
Where, where, where are y'all living right now?
A living.
Turns out they're not giving SNAP to anybody.
There we go.
Even, even worse.
Do you understand where you live?
Thank you.
It's Carly Monet.
Like they're doing whatever they want.
The government is not, do you, okay.
Congress is who controls the purse.
So there are three branches of government.
The executive branch, the judicial branch, the legislative branch.
The executive branch is the presidency.
The judicial branch is the SCOTUS, the Supreme Court of the United States.
The legislative branch is Congress.
Congress controls the purse and the constitution in terms of creating the extensions to the constitution.
So acts, bills, laws, all right?
On a federal level.
When I say controls the purse, it means that once the United States of America, you pay your federal taxes, Congress determines how those taxes are allocated.
That's what's happening right now is that they could not agree on a budget for taxes and allocation because the version of the budget that they created does not tax the rich, but it cuts severely the ability for people to get Medicaid and Medicare.
And so the Democrats were like, well, then we're just not going to agree on it at all because you guys are going to make these cuts that you promised you weren't going to make.
However, they also are the determiners of how much money goes to other places.
So they send money to other countries.
They fund programs that send money and other things to other countries.
They also fund agencies.
Now, what a lot of people don't know is that though Congress controls the purse, there's a whole other secret purse that the CIA controls.
The president has money in that purse that he gets to spend that is not on the books on the Congress.
Okay, they have money that they have on the side that they use for assassinations, that they use to fund militias and other countries to create destabilization.
The entire goal of the United States is to preserve power by destabilizing everywhere else in the world in a multitude of ways, militarily, medically, food insecurity, etc.
So Congress is somewhat of a front in that way, because there's a whole geopolitical effort that's happening beyond Congress.
However, in the present day, we are seeing that the efforts that the CIA does geopolitically, they're doing that right here to us in America.
They are destabilizing the United States militarily, medically, and with food insecurity.
This is the imperial boomerang.
They're doing it to everywhere else, and they realize that in order to continue their gain, they have to come back and do it to us, because capitalism eats itself.
It knows no limits.
So eventually, it eats itself.
Then you have SCOTUS.
SCOTUS is the executive branch.
I mean, it's the legislative branch.
Sorry, the judicial branch.
I apologize.
SCOTUS is the judicial branch.
The judicial branch is who basically upholds the Constitution.
However, at the end of the day, they are dictators, because they are not elected officials, and they get to serve on the bench for life.
They also have very, very, very limited checks and balances.
It is incredibly difficult to impeach a member of SCOTUS.
So the judicial branch at present is even further infiltrated because we know that it has been overrun with folks who are absolutely aligned with a dark money, dark movement that is controlling the executive branch.
The executive branch is who is supposed to enforce what happens in SCOTUS and what happens in the legislative branch.
They are supposed to be the ones who say, okay, in order for this to happen, we need to make sure that the populace is behaving a certain way.
But people have been tricked into thinking that the president is somehow their friend or their representative.
No, the president is HR.
The president does not represent the people.
The president represents the country.
And anybody who's ever worked in corporate knows that when you go to HR and you try to complain, like, come on, you know, you're supposed to represent us.
HR is like, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And then some shit go down with you.
So when I see folks being like, oh, I sound weird as heck, because those people do not even see you.
You are a populace to them.
You are a number amongst many.
And you are literally just what they are using to uphold the power of the United States with powers, the wealth and power of a few.
That's it.
This country is also too fucking big.
There's no reason that this country should be this big.
Its footprint is not, it's not even manageable.
And someone here is like, I love Kamala Harris.
You sound like an idiot.
And you're the same person who said, I want my SNAP benefits.
And you like that Kamala Harris is out here cursing out the Republicans for cutting your SNAP benefits.
When she ran on an entire campaign that didn't even consider you.
Her whole campaign completely ignored the working class.
It had absolutely no interest in preserving you.
Her whole campaign was about Republicans who were not MAGA and the middle class and keeping the United States the most lethal army alive.
So why do you love Kamala Harris?
She also, when she was the DA and the, sorry, when she was the, the AG and the DA was really a cop who is obviously going to focus more on those who have leased the laced resources.
Because that is what the policing system does.
They're going to focus on the poor, the black, the brown.
It's built into the actual system.
So it is odd to me for folks to love somebody who has chosen a path that by nature of its existence is meant to harm you.
So now we're here in the middle of this mayhem and you got folks who can't see who their enemies are, who can't see the path forward, who can't even understand how deep in the quicksand they are.
And I get so afraid that I won't see us pull ourselves out because you have not committed yourself to decolonizing yourself because you don't even believe that you've been indoctrinated.
And that's all this country has done for the past 60 years is trick you.
That's what it's been doing.
And the only reason that someone like me was able to get out from under it is because I am neurodivergent.
Even if you're not neurodivergent, you too can get out from under it.
It's just that I have a brain that is wired a particular way that makes it difficult to doctrinate.
So I will be out in the world this week.
Oh my God.
I think sometimes y'all are either bots or you just want to see me lose my fucking mind.
Because after I said all of that, someone on here said, who are we going for then?
And I'm going to assume you're a bot.
So I'm not going to address you directly.
But what my point is, there's no one to go for.
Everything we're doing right now is habit.
It is simply habit.
Voting, all of this is habit.
And we're just, we're doing it because we don't know anything else to do.
So I'm not judging.
But it is habit.
And I wonder when you're going to see that these habits of ours keep us from doing anything different.
So if you want to come talk and be in community with folks, I hope that you will come out to one of these cities that I'm going to be at.
I hope that you don't let these Zionists make you stay home in fear.
Because all they got is words.
I hope that you will join us on Wednesday mornings on Views from Amanda Land at 10 a.m. Eastern to work on getting out of the indoctrination that they have put you in in this nation.
I hope if you have fear, you will face it.
You will question it.
You will become curious about it.
Y'all think I sit in this fucking house all day.
And that's not what's happening here.
But I'll see you out there in the world.
And I hope if you see me, whether it's at a restaurant or on the plane or whatever, I hope you, you know what I'm saying?
I hope we do that to each other.
Again, if you have an extra $40 to send a turkey to the church here in Nyack, I would be much appreciative.
I will post this to my stories.
I really wish I could have solved the entire problem of getting them 100 turkeys.
I wasn't able to do it, but I would love to be able to get them some.
I will be on with Brianna Joy Gray tonight, 7 p.m. Eastern on YouTube.
So I hope you will join and we'll be talking about the election here in New York.
I'm not sure what you just go on Walmart or wherever and you buy a turkey and you deliver it to this to the church.
I don't want to deal with people's money.
Go on a site where you can buy a turkey or the turkey and have it delivered to the church.
Because I do not want to collect people's money.
And I just ahead of time, I want to thank all of the venues that have seen the value in me coming to their space.
And also understand the necessity for me to hold on to 100% of my book earnings, considering I have put 100% into the book.
I'm very proud of myself.
I'm very proud of this work.
I hope that you'll be really moved by the new staging that we're doing for the live stream on Saturday.
If you haven't got your ticket, go to AmandaSeals.com.
And shout out to For Your Viewing Pleasure and Jenin Matari for the Israel is a settler colony.
And yes, I did buy the shirt.
They did not donate to me.
And this is on my hand so that I can remember to do something.
Because if I don't do it here, I'll forget.
So every time I see this, it reminds me you have something to do.
Wish you all the best.
I'll see you in the world.